http://www.pdflib.com/privacy/

skip navigation
DE
Suche:
ProductsProduct OverviewPDFlib Product FamilyOverviewPDFlibPDFlib+PDIPDFlib Personalization Server (PPS)Feature ComparisonFeatures in PDFlib 9Use CasesPDFlib on mobile and embedded PlatformsPricesTETOverviewNew FeaturesFeaturesAdvantages for Text ExtractionAdvantages for Image ExtractionHow to use TETTET on mobile and embedded PlatformsPricesTET PDF IFilterOverviewFeaturesPricesTET PluginPLOPFeaturesPricesPLOP DSFeaturesPricespCOS InterfaceMobile and EmbeddedFontReporterDownloadPDFlib Product FamilyBlock PluginTETTET PDF IFilterTET PluginPLOP and PLOP DSFree SoftwareTET PluginFontReporterCMapsLicensing & SupportLicensingSupportSupport DetailsLicense Keys and Minor ReleasesMajor UpdatesMinor UpdatesProduct LifetimePremium LicensesOpening a Support CaseCookbooksPDFlib CookbookTET CookbookpCOS CookbookDocumentationManualsHowTosWhitepapersAIX Binaries on iSeriesPDF Knowledge BasePDF 2.0What to expect from PDF 2.0?Existing Acrobat FeaturesExisting Features from PDF StandardsNew CapabilitiesDeprecated FeaturesWhat's missing in PDF 2.0?PDF Password SecurityPDF Password SecurityEncryptionPermissionsRecommendationsPDF Certificate SecurityPDF Certificate SecurityCMS Enveloped DataCryptographic DetailsUse CasesPDF/AThe PDF/A StandardsTechnical ConceptsPDF/A ViewersProcessing PDF/APDF/A in PDFlibPDF/UAThe PDF/UA StandardWCAG 2.0Tagged PDF BasicsRequirementsMatterhorn ProtocolPDF/UA ReadersPDF/UA in PDFlibPDF/VTFuture ISO StandardsPDF/X Output IntentsZUGFeRD and Factur-XXMPXMP OverviewXMP in PDF/AFree XMP ValidatorAbout UsContactSite NoticePrivacy PolicyBuyDirect SalesOrder ProcessPurchase order formsVolume discountsVATOnline ShopPDFlib, PDFlib+PDI, PPSPDFlib TETPDFlib TET PDF IFilterPDFlib PLOPPDFlib PLOP DSResellers
ProductsProduct OverviewPDFlib Product FamilyOverviewPDFlibPDFlib+PDIPDFlib Personalization Server (PPS)Feature ComparisonFeatures in PDFlib 9Use CasesPDFlib on mobile and embedded PlatformsPricesTETOverviewNew FeaturesFeaturesAdvantages for Text ExtractionAdvantages for Image ExtractionHow to use TETTET on mobile and embedded PlatformsPricesTET PDF IFilterOverviewFeaturesPricesTET PluginPLOPFeaturesPricesPLOP DSFeaturesPricespCOS InterfaceMobile and EmbeddedFontReporterDownloadPDFlib Product FamilyBlock PluginTETTET PDF IFilterTET PluginPLOP and PLOP DSFree SoftwareTET PluginFontReporterCMapsLicensing & SupportLicensingSupportSupport DetailsLicense Keys and Minor ReleasesMajor UpdatesMinor UpdatesProduct LifetimePremium LicensesOpening a Support CaseCookbooksPDFlib CookbookTET CookbookpCOS CookbookDocumentationManualsHowTosWhitepapersAIX Binaries on iSeriesPDF Knowledge BasePDF 2.0What to expect from PDF 2.0?Existing Acrobat FeaturesExisting Features from PDF StandardsNew CapabilitiesDeprecated FeaturesWhat's missing in PDF 2.0?PDF Password SecurityPDF Password SecurityEncryptionPermissionsRecommendationsPDF Certificate SecurityPDF Certificate SecurityCMS Enveloped DataCryptographic DetailsUse CasesPDF/AThe PDF/A StandardsTechnical ConceptsPDF/A ViewersProcessing PDF/APDF/A in PDFlibPDF/UAThe PDF/UA StandardWCAG 2.0Tagged PDF BasicsRequirementsMatterhorn ProtocolPDF/UA ReadersPDF/UA in PDFlibPDF/VTFuture ISO StandardsPDF/X Output IntentsZUGFeRD and Factur-XXMPXMP OverviewXMP in PDF/AFree XMP ValidatorAbout UsContactSite NoticePrivacy PolicyBuyDirect SalesOrder ProcessPurchase order formsVolume discountsVATOnline ShopPDFlib, PDFlib+PDI, PPSPDFlib TETPDFlib TET PDF IFilterPDFlib PLOPPDFlib PLOP DSResellers
Deutsch
Privacy Policy
PDFlib GmbHPrivacy Policy
1. General information and mandatory informationOpposition to promotional emailsWe hereby expressly prohibit the use of contact data published in the context of website legal notice requirements with regard to sending promotional and informational materials not expressly requested. The website operator reserves the right to take specific legal action if unsolicited advertising material, such as email spam, is received.2. Data collection on our websiteCookiesSome of our web pages use cookies. Cookies do not harm your computer and do not contain any viruses. Cookies help make our website more user-friendly, efficient, and secure. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer and saved by your browser.Most of the cookies we use are so-called "session cookies." They are automatically deleted after your visit. Other cookies remain in your device's memory until you delete them. These cookies make it possible to recognize your browser when you next visit the site.You can configure your browser to inform you about the use of cookies so that you can decide on a case-by-case basis whether to accept or reject a cookie. Alternatively, your browser can be configured to automatically accept cookies under certain conditions or to always reject them, or to automatically delete cookies when closing your browser. Disabling cookies may limit the functionality of this website.Cookies which are necessary to allow electronic communications or to provide certain functions you wish to use (such as the shopping cart) are stored pursuant to Art. 6 paragraph 1, letter f of DSGVO. The website operator has a legitimate interest in the storage of cookies to ensure an optimized service provided free of technical errors. If other cookies (such as those used to analyze your surfing behavior) are also stored, they will be treated separately in this privacy policy.Server log filesThe website provider automatically collects and stores information that your browser automatically transmits to us in "server log files". These are:Browser type and browser versionOperating system usedReferrer URLHost name of the accessing computerTime of the server requestIP addressThese data will not be combined with data from other sources.The basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) (b) DSGVO, which allows the processing of data to fulfill a contract or for measures preliminary to a contract.3. Analytics and advertisingGoogle AnalyticsThis website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service. It is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.Google Analytics uses so-called "cookies". These are text files that are stored on your computer and that allow an analysis of the use of the website by you. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is usually transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there.Google Analytics cookies are stored based on Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO. The website operator has a legitimate interest in analyzing user behavior to optimize both its website and its advertising.For more information about how Google Analytics handles user data, see Google's privacy policy.IP anonymizationWe have activated the IP anonymization feature on this website. Your IP address will be shortened by Google within the European Union or other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area prior to transmission to the United States. Only in exceptional cases is the full IP address sent to a Google server in the US and shortened there. Google will use this information on behalf of the operator of this website to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports on website activity, and to provide other services regarding website activity and Internet usage for the website operator. The IP address transmitted by your browser as part of Google Analytics will not be merged with any other data held by Google. Browser pluginYou can prevent these cookies being stored by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser. However, we wish to point out that doing so may mean you will not be able to enjoy the full functionality of this website. You can also prevent the data generated by cookies about your use of the website (incl. your IP address) from being passed to Google, and the processing of these data by Google, by downloading and installing the browser plugin.
Google AdWords and Google Conversion TrackingThis website uses Google AdWords. AdWords is an online advertising program from Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, United States ("Google").As part of Google AdWords, we use so-called conversion tracking. When you click on an ad served by Google, a conversion tracking cookie is set. Cookies are small text files that your internet browser stores on your computer. These cookies expire after 30 days and are not used for personal identification of the user. Should the user visit certain pages of the website and the cookie has not yet expired, Google and the website can tell that the user clicked on the ad and proceeded to that page.Each Google AdWords advertiser has a different cookie. Thus, cookies cannot be tracked using the website of an AdWords advertiser. The information obtained using the conversion cookie is used to create conversion statistics for the AdWords advertisers who have opted for conversion tracking. Customers are told the total number of users who clicked on their ad and were redirected to a conversion tracking tag page. However, advertisers do not obtain any information that can be used to personally identify users. If you do not want to participate in tracking, you can opt-out of this by easily disabling the Google Conversion Tracking cookie by changing your browser settings. In doing so, you will not be included in the conversion tracking statistics.Conversion cookies are stored based on Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO. The website operator has a legitimate interest in analyzing user behavior to optimize both its website and its advertising.For more information about Google AdWords and Google Conversion Tracking, see the Google Privacy Policy.You can configure your browser to inform you about the use of cookies so that you can decide on a case-by-case basis whether to accept or reject a cookie. Alternatively, your browser can be configured to automatically accept cookies under certain conditions or to always reject them, or to automatically delete cookies when closing your browser. Disabling cookies may limit the functionality of this website.
